// Geography Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A small body from which a planet originated in the solar system's early development?",
    answer: "Planetesimal",
    options: [
      "Outgassing",
      "Solar Nebula",
      "Planetesimal",
      "Protoplanet"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A rotating cloud of gas and dust that gave rise to Earth's solar system",
    answer: "Protoplanet",
    options: [
      "Core Planet",
      "Protoplanet",
      "Solar Nebula",
      "Outgassing"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A planet similar to Earth in size, mass & density",
    answer: "Venus",
    options: [
      "Mars",
      "Uranus",
      "Venus",
      "Jupiter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A planet with massive volcanoes and canyons; seasons are similar to Earth's",
    answer: "Mars",
    options: [
      "Pluto",
      "Mars",
      "Venus",
      "Jupiter"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The only planet with the proper combination of water, atmosphere, and temperature to support life",
    answer: "Earth",
    options: [
      "Neptune",
      "Earth",
      "Uranus",
      "Jupiter"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The planet closest to the sun; has a hot, heavily-cratered surface",
  answer: "Mercury",
  options: [
    "Venus",
    "Mars",
    "Mercury",
    "Earth"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "The satellite that orbited Venus",
  answer: "Magellan",
  options: [
    "Explorer",
    "Magellan",
    "Hailey's Comet",
    "Hubbell"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "A ring of debris that separates the inner planets from the outer planets",
  answer: "Asteroid belt",
  options: [
    "Gas giant",
    "Asteroid belt",
    "Asteroid",
    "Comet"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "A planet with a complex rind system made of dust and icy debris",
  answer: "Saturn",
  options: [
    "Jupiter",
    "Saturn",
    "Uranus",
    "Neptune"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "The largest planet in the solar system, has alternating light and dark bands",
  answer: "Jupiter",
  options: [
    "Earth",
    "Saturn",
    "Venus",
    "Jupiter"
  ]
},

];
